So far, we've been stimulating event outcomes by generating
حتى الآن، كنا نحاكي مخرجات الحدث عن طريق تكوين
random numbers with NumPy's random.randint and random.choice.
أرقام عشوائية مع NumPy's random.randint و random.choice.
However, there is a better function for
بالرغم من ذلك، توجد وظيفة أفضل
simulating large binomial experiments like coin flips.
لمحاكاة التجارب الثنائية مثل قلب العملة.
Here, you see NumPy's random.binomial function,
هنا، ترى وظيفة NumPy's random.binomial،
which simulates a number of events n,
التي تحاكي عدد من الأحداث N،
which each have probability of success p.
والتي لديها احتمالية النجاح p.
Success just represents one of the two outcomes of the event.
يمثل النجاح إحدى مُخرجّي الحدث.
Really, either outcome could be the success.
حقًا، إحدى المخرجات قد يكون النجاح.
For example, if our event is flipping a fair coin 10 times,
على سبيل المثال، إذا كان الحدث يقلب العملة 10 مرات،
we could define success as the number of heads.
يمكننا تحديد النجاح كعدد الصور.
n would be the number of flips.
قد يكون N عدد المرات التي تنقلب فيها العملة.
In this case, 10,
في هذه الحالة، 10
and p would be the probability of heads for each flip which is 0.5.
و p قد تكون احتمالية الصور لكل مرة تنقلب فيها والتي هي 0.5.
To try this out,
لتجربة ذلك،
let's set n equal to 10 and p equal to 0.5.
لنجعل n تساوي 10 و p تساوي 0.5.
Notice, this returns 1 integer instead of an array of 10 outcomes.
لاحظ، يعيد ذلك عدد صحيح واحد بدلاً من مصفوفة من 10 مخرجات.
Since this function is only for binomial outcomes,
بما أن الوظيفة هي مخرجات ثنائية فقط،
it can simplify the output by just returning the number of successes.
يمكنها تبسيط المُخرج بإعادة رقم عمليات النجاح.
In this case, 4.
في هذه الحالة، 4.
This is the number of heads.
هذا هو عدد الصور.
Again, we can run the simulation many times.
مرة أخرى، يمكننا إجراء المحاكاة عدة مرات.
Let's run this 20 times.
لنجريها 20 مرة.
Each number in this array represents the number of
يمثل كل رقم في هذه المصفوفة عدد
heads that resulted from each test of 10 coin flips.
الصور التي نتجت عن كل محاولة لعشر مرات تنقلب فيها العملة.
This is the number of heads on the first 10 coin flips,
هذا عدد الصور في أول 10 مرات تنقلب فيها العملة،
while this one is the number on the second 10 coin flips and so on,
بينما هذا هو عدد المرات العشر في الثانية التي تنقلب فيها العملة وهكذا،
for 20 different flippings of the coin.
في 20 مرة مختلفة تنقلب فيها العملة.
Let's find the mean number of heads for these tests.
لنجد متوسط عدد الصوة لهذه المحاولات.
Since this is a fair coin,
بما أن هذه عملة،
we would expect this mean to be close to 5.
نتوقع أن يكون هذا المتوسط قريب من 5.
You can see that this is a little bit of a ways away,
يمكنك رؤية أن هذه مجموعة قليلة الطرق،
probably because we only ran 20 tests.
يُحتمل أنه بسبب أننا أجرينا 20 محاولة فقط.
Let's see what happens if we increase the number of tests.
لنرى ماذا يحدث لو إذا قمنا بزيادة عدد المحاولات.
Since these events are random,
بما أن هذه الأحداث عشوائية،
it's not guaranteed that each simulation will perfectly average five heads.
لا نضمن أن يكون متوسط كل محاكاة خمسة صور بالضبط.
However, as this number of tests increase,
بالرغم من ذلك، بينما يزيد عدد المحاولات،
the simulation more closely reflects the fairness of the coin.
تعكس المحاكاة إنصاف العملة بشكل أفضل.
With 10,000 tests, the mean is much closer to five heads.
مع 10000 محاولة، يقترب المتوسط من 5 صور.
Let's use matplotlib to plot a histogram of the outcomes in this simulation.
لنستخدم matplotlib لرسم مدرج تكراري للمخرجات في هذه المحاكاة.
As expected, the distribution is centered around five heads.
كما هو متوقع، يتمركز التوزيع حول 5 صور.